## Andrés Zapata Mazo Full stack software developer

Medellín, Colombia, +57 3118203192, andrez.mazo@gmail.com

LINKS	inkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/andrezmazo itHub: www.github.com/andrezmazo	
PROFILE	Web Developer with 2+ years of experience. Proficient in JavaScript, React.js, PHP, MySQL, Redux.js, Node.js, and more. Leadership, adaptability, and teamwork skills. Eager to tackle new challenges.	

### RECENT EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

MAY 2023 - Present Medellín, Colombia

Full stack developer freelance, ATV - ANTIVIRUS PARA LA DESERCIÓN

Front End and Back End development for the creation of a web platform in React.js with user interfaces, scheduling, and academic records aimed at multiple Universities in Valle del Aburra, with relational

databases in MySQL. Maintenance of PHP platform. Notable skills:

React.js, JavaScript, PHP, MySQL, Redux.js, CSS, Node.js, Express.js, HTML, REST API, Google API, Data Analysis, Requirements Analysis, Scrum.

AUGUST 2022 - MAY 2023 Medellín, Colombia

Full stack developer freelance, SATMED - SISTEMA DE ALERTAS TEMPRANAS DE MEDELLÍN

Front End and Back End development for maintenance and update of web platform for registration and characterization of Medellin alert situations. Developed in VUE, responsive design in Bootstrap, and Node.js for the Back End, TypeScript-based environment. Additionally, implementation of a robust REST

API and efficient use of MySQL.

Notable skills:

VUE Js, TypeScript, JavaScript, MySQL, CSS, Node Js, API-REST, Bootstrap, TypeScript, Express Js, HTML, Scrum.

FEBRUARY 2022 - AUGUST Full stack developer freelance, SISCARAC

2022

Medellín, Colombia

Front End and Back End development for the implementation of new population characterization features for Antioquia's web platform and mobile application on Play Store. Developed in Angular, .NET, Node.js for the backend, TypeScript-based environment. REST API and data storage and management in MySQL.

Notable skills:

Angular, .NET, Ionic, Cordova, JavaScript, TypeScript, Android, Play Store, MySQL, CSS, Node.js, Express Js, HTML, API REST, Scrum.

### **EDUCATION**

NOVEMBER 2022 - JUNE 2023 ORACLE NEXT EDUCATION BACK, Alura Latam - Oracle.

AUGUST 2022 - OCTOBER 2022 DATA SCIENCE, La Escuela Superior de Administración Pública.

Course

NOVEMBER 2021 - JUNE 2022 FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER, Digital House -Argentina.

JANUARY 2013 - AUGUST 2018 SOUND ENGINEERING, University of San Buenaventura, Medellín

Professional degree

Multiple certifications Platzi, Avixa, Dante, Bosch, Electrovoice, Dynacord, and more.

LANGUAGES	English B2	Cnanich Nativo	Dortuguese A2
LANGUAGES	English, B2	Spanish, Native	Portuguese, A2
	C1 Smart Language Academy (2023 - Ongoing)		Private classes
	B1 University of San Buenaventura		

## **SKILLS**

FRONT END JavaScript, TypeScript, React Js, VUE, Angular, CSS, SASS, Bootstrap, EJS and HTML.

BACK END JavaScript, TypeScript, Node Js, MySQL, Express Js, PHP, JAVA, Redux, data-base analysis and management. **DEVOPS** Scrum and Kanban

SOFT SKILSS Leadership, adaptability, determination, efficiency, teamwork, transparent communication, problem-solving, respect for diverse perspectives, willingness to learn.

REFERENCES

JUAN HERNANDEZ, ATV, SATMED, SISCARAC. IT SECURITY CONSULTANT | SENIOR FULL STACK DEVELOPER +57 322 387 3379

ANDRÉS JARAMILLO. CLOUD GAIA. CLOUD DEVELOPER

+57 300 469 0360

JUAN MONTOYA, AMBIENTES INTELIGENTES. CEO

+57 310 410 8076

# Andrés Zapata Mazo Full stack software developer

Medellín, Colombia, +57 3118203192, andrez.mazo@gmail.com

### EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

APRIL 2023 - DECEMBER

2023

Medellín, Colombia

Engineering director, Ambientes inteligentes

Directing, coordinating, evaluating, and leading the engineering and development area in projects invol-

ving audio, video, programming, and automation with a UX/UI focus.

Notable skills:

Visual Basic, automation, leadership, project management, Bosch, Kanban, UX/UI, Ease Acoustics, Ease

Address, Ease Focus, Autocad, CUE, Symetrix, UDP, TCP/IP, RS 232, Dante, Office.

DECEMBER 2020 - APRIL

2023

Medellín, Colombia

Project engineer, Ambientes inteligentes

Development, design, programming, and project management of audio, video, and UX/UI automation

projects. Notable skills:

Visual Basic, automation, project management, Kanban, UX/UI, Ease Acoustics, Ease Address, Ease

Focus, Autocad, CUE, Symetrix, UDP, TCP/IP, RS 232, Dante, Office.

DECEMBER 2017- MARCH

2020

Medellín, Colombia

Project director, Acustega

Direction, development, modeling, rendering, simulation, design, and evaluation of architectural

acoustics projects, noise studies, and noise control. Coordinating and

supervising carpentry, white work, electro-luminous, and finishes.

Notable skills:

Project management, AutoCAD, Lumion, SketchUp, Vray, Ease Acoustics, Ease Address, Ease Focus,

Insul, Photoshop, Office.